{
    "subject": "resource/It's_All_About_the_Stragglers",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "It's All About the Stragglers",
    "human_readable": "The label of 'It's All About the Stragglers' is 'It's All About the Stragglers'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9843822121620178,
            "question": "What is the label 'It's All About the Stragglers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9671880602836609,
            "question": "Is there a title associated with 'It's All About the Stragglers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.966036856174469,
            "question": "Does the label 'It's All About the Stragglers' describe something specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8890448808670044,
            "question": "Is there any other information we need to understand the meaning of 'It's All About the Stragglers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8847603797912598,
            "question": "How does the simplicity of the label 'It's All About the Stragglers' contribute to its meaning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8696372509002686,
            "question": "What is your interpretation of the phrase 'It's All About the Stragglers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677995800971985,
            "question": "What might the phrase 'It's All About the Stragglers' suggest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8203516006469727,
            "question": "Could you give an example of a situation where the phrase 'It's All About the Stragglers' might be used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8185449242591858,
            "question": "Could 'It's All About the Stragglers' be a title of a book, movie, or song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1378639042377472,
            "question": "What kind of context would help us better understand this label?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of 'It's All About the Stragglers' is 'It's All About the Stragglers'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2123_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could 'It's All About the Stragglers' be a title of a book, movie, or song?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2123_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you give an example of a situation where the phrase 'It's All About the Stragglers' might be used?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2123_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might the phrase 'It's All About the Stragglers' suggest?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2123_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2123_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, the label of 'It's All About the Stragglers' is actually \"London Records\", not \"It's All About the Stragglers\" itself. This can be seen in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2123/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt, where it says \"Label: London Records\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provided contain information about an album titled \"It's All About The Stragglers\" by Artful Dodger. Specifically, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2123/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt lists the title of the CD album as \"It's All About The Stragglers\". Therefore, the label 'It's All About the Stragglers' for the album matches the statement given in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The label of 'It's All About the Stragglers' is not named 'It's All About the Stragglers'. The correct label is London Records.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context states the label of \"It's All About The Stragglers\" is London Records.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The label of \"It's All About the Stragglers\" is actually listed as London Records, not \"It's All About the Stragglers\".",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}